RASHONDA WILLIAMS, RN

8618 Granville Drive, Dallas, TX 75249 ◆ (214) 240-1888 ◆ nursero8@yahoo.com
PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY
Texas Board-Certified Registered Nurse with over 5 years of experience delivering high-quality care to patients in PACU, PICU and Medical-Surgical care units. Well organized and forward thinking in managing patient needs while providing excellent customer service.
Work History

Registered Nurse, 07/2017 to Current

Med Temp Now – Dallas, TX

- Monitored patient condition, including interpreting and tracking EKG readings, identifying irregular telemetry readings and updating team members on changes in stability or acuity
- Observed and reported patient condition, progress and medication side effects to accurately document updates
- Accurately documented all elements of nursing assessment, including treatment, medications and IVs administered, discharge instructions and follow-up care
- Managed patients recovering from medical or surgical procedures, including facilitating wound care, ostomy care, pressure ulcer prevention and pain management

Psychiatric Registered Nurse, 07/2016 to Current

Medical City Green Oaks – Dallas, United States

- Facilitated therapeutic communication, conflict resolution and crisis intervention by redirecting negative behaviors and helping patients regain or improve coping abilities to prevent further disability
- Administered medications and treatment to patients and monitored responses while working with healthcare teams to adjust care plans
- Taught patients how to improve lifestyle choices, dramatically reducing chance of symptom reoccurrence
- Partnered with physicians, social workers, activity therapists, nutritionists and case managers to develop
 and implement individualized care plans and documented all patient interactions and interventions in
 electronic charting systems

Registered Nurse, 07/2015 to 07/2018

Total Med Staffing – Appleton, WI

- Maintained quality care and comfort for patients with heart failure, pulmonary hypertension and other conditions
- Collaborated with interdisciplinary healthcare personnel to meet patients' personal, physical, psychological and cognitive needs
- Partnered with physicians, social workers, activity therapists, nutritionists and case managers to develop and implement individualized care plans and documented all patient interactions and interventions in electronic charting systems
- Provided direct patient care, stabilized patients and determined next course of action

EDUCATION —
ssociate of Science: Nursing, 2015
amar State College - Port Arthur - Port Arthur, TX
achelor of Science: Nursing, 2019 he University of Texas At Arlington - Arlington, TX
SKILLS —

• CPR/ACLS certified